webgameapp.com 2018-11-27

# Privacy Policy - WebGameApp.com

Privacy Policy for Webgamesapp

  If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at Webgamesapp@gmail.com

At Webgamesapp we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by Webgamesapp and how we use it.

We acquire, hold, use, and Process Personal Information based on the legal grounds and for the legitimate business purposes outlined in this Policy, such as

To Provide Services or Information Requested

Webgamesapp may use information about you to fulfill requests for Services or information, including information about potential or future Services, including to:Generally manage Individual information and accounts; Respond to questions, comments, and other requests;Provide access to certain areas, functionalities, and features of Webgamesapp's Services or Website;Allow you to register for events.

Administrative Purposes

Webgamesapp may use Personal Information about you for its administrative purposes, including to: Ensure you have a personalized and consistent experience in using the Website and Services;Protect the security of our Service and Websiteand to prevent fraud;Measure interest in Webgamesapp Services b and perform analytics;Notify you of changes to the Website or Services;Develop new Services;Ensure internal quality control;Verify Individual identity;Communicate about Individual accounts and activities on amingToStudio's Services, Website and systems, and, in Webgamesapp discretion, changes to any Webgamesapp policy;Send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance;Process payment for Services purchased;Process applications and transactions;Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;Enforce our Terms of Use.

Research and Development

 Webgamesapp may use Personal Information to create non-identifiable information that we may use alone or in the aggregate with information obtained from other sources, in order to help us improve our Website, to optimally deliver our existing Services or develop new Services. From time to time, Webgamesapp may perform research (online and offline) via surveys. We may engage Third-Party service providers to conduct such surveys on our behalf. All survey responses are voluntary, and the information collected will be used for research and reporting purposes to help us better serve Individuals by learning more about their needs and the quality of the Services we provide. The survey responses may be utilized to determine the effectiveness of our Services or our Website, various types of communications, advertising campaigns, and/or promotional activities. If an Individual participates in a survey, the information given will be used along with that of other study participants. We may share anonymous Individual and aggregate data for research and analysis purposes.

Direct Mail, Email and Outbound Telemarketing

Individuals who provide us with Personal Information, or whose Personal Information we obtain from Third Parties, may receive periodic emails, newsletters, mailings, or phone calls from us with information on Webgamesapp or our business partners’ products and services or upcoming special offers/events we believe may be of interest. We offer the option to decline these communications at no cost to the Individual by following the instructions in Section 6 below.

Mobile Devices

Webgamesapp provides Services that are specifically designed to be compatible and used on mobile Devices. Webgamesapp will collect certain information that your mobile Device sends when you use such Services, like a GPS location, user settings and the operating system of your Device. Webgamesapp Services require that users log in with an account, and information collected through mobile versions of the Services is associated with user accounts. In addition, Webgamesapp may enable Individuals to download an application, widget, or other tool that can be used on Devices. Some of these tools may store information on Devices. These tools may transmit Personal Information to Webgamesapp to enable Individuals to access user accounts and to enable Webgamesapp  to track use of these tools. Some of these tools may enable users to email reports and other information from the tool. Webgamesapp may use personal or non-identifiable information transmitted to Webgamesapp to enhance these tools, to develop new tools, for quality improvement and as otherwise described in this Policy or in other notices Webgamesapp provides.

Anonymous and Aggregated Information

Webgamesapp may use Personal Information and other information about you to create anonymized and aggregated information, such as de-identified demographic information, de-identified location information, information about the Device from which you access Webgamesapp Services or Website, or other analyses we create. Anonymized and aggregated information is used for a variety of functions, including the measurement of visitors’ interest in and use of various portions or features of the Services or Website. Anonymized or aggregated information is not Personal Information, and Webgamesapp may use such information in a number of ways, including research, internal analysis, analytics, and any other legally permissible purposes. We may share this information within Webgamesapp and with Third Parties for our or their purposes in an anonymized or aggregated form that is designed to prevent anyone from identifying you.

Sharing Content with Friends or Colleagues

Webgamesapp Services may offer various tools and functionality. For example, Webgamesapp may provide functionality on its Services that will allow you to forward or share certain content with a friend or colleague. Email addresses that you may provide for a friend or colleague will be used to send your friend or colleague the content or link you request, but will not be collected or otherwise used by Webgamesapp or any other Third Parties for any other purpose.

Other Uses

Webgamesapp may use Personal Information for other purposes for which we have a legitimate interest, such as direct marketing, individual or market research, anti-fraud protection, or any other purpose disclosed to you at the time you provide Personal Information or with your consent.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, Webgamesapp makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
Webgamesapp uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Webgamesapp.  
→ Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to Webgamesapp and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Our Advertising Partners  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......

Google

While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here: Privacy Policies.  
You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of Webgamesapp.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Webgamesapp and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

Webgamesapp has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Third Party Privacy Policies  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Webgamesapp."'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. What Are Cookies?

Children's Information  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. Webgamesapp does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that Webgamesapp has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

Online Privacy Policy Only  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

Consent  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

Privacy Policy Online Approved Site

Update  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Sunday, May 27th, 2018. Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
